// Question Types
// 1. MCQs | Multiple Choice | single
// 2. boolean | true/false | single
// 3. MAQs | Multiple Answers | multiple

import { Topic } from '.'

export const Q015: Topic = {
  topic: 'TOEIC Part 5',
  level: 'Beginner',
  totalQuestions: 10,
  totalScore: 10,
  totalTime: 100,
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'It is said that older people tend ------ more TV than younger people.',
      choices: ['watching', 'watch', 'to be watched', 'to watch'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['watch'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'Ms. Okada had to ------ the job offer from KAOA Motors because she had already decided to work for another company.',
      choices: ['decline', 'resume', 'preserve', 'misplace'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['decline'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: '------ the books Ｍr. Kamau ordered arrive at the store, please give him a call.',
      choices: ['Following', 'Immediately', 'Regarding', 'As soon as'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['as'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'If you are looking for ------ information on bicycle repair, please check out the videos on the repair related pages of our website.',
      choices: ['helpfulness', 'helps', 'helpful', 'helpfully'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['helpful'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'The Asian Furniture Expo will be held ------ the Tokyo Bay Convention Center from June 11 to 15.',
      choices: ['from', 'at', 'over', 'of'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['at'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'Mr. Valdez created the new product concept after a thorough ------ of market research data.',
      choices: ['analyst', 'analysis', 'analyzed', 'analyze'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['analysis'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'Podell Electronics is trying to gather as ------ customer comments as possible for new product development.',
      choices: ['another', 'many', 'each of', 'much'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['many'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'Our pharmacy will be closed tomorrow, so please bring the ------ from your doctor after the day after tomorrow.',
      choices: ['subscription', 'participation', 'comparison', 'prescription'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['prescription'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'Please make sure that the audio equipment in Conference Room 203 is working ------ for tomorrow’s presentation.',
      choices: ['more proper', 'properly', 'proper', 'properness'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['properly'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'The results will be compiled ------ as one month has already passed since the survey was mailed.',
      choices: ['previously', 'shortly', 'proudly', 'nearly'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['shortly'],
      score: 1,
    },
  ],
}